Viewers all over the world,
wherever that disease is located in your body, never a sickness Jesus cannot heal.
Never a disease Jesus cannot cure; never a burden Jesus cannot bear.
I command that disease to leave you, in the name of Jesus-
to leave your blood, in the name of Jesus, to leave your kidneys, in the name of Jesus,
to leave your liver, in the name of Jesus,
to leave your bones, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever name you call it, never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Be cured, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Leave my people!
Open your lips and say, "Leave me, in the name of Jesus!"
You disease, I command you to lave me in the name of Jesus!
You sickness, I command you to leave me, in the name of Jesus!
You infirmity, I command you to leave me, in the name of Jesus!
Leave me, in the name of Jesus!
Prayer!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
God says it is time for you to leave.
You disease - it is time for you to leave.
You affliction - it is time for you to leave.
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
It is time to leave!
Leave!
You affliction in the bones, you affliction in the kidneys, you affliction in the liver,
you affliction in the blood - it is time to leave!
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
Command, "Leave!"
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command you to leave!
Viewers, all over the world, I see them leaving.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I am seeing them leaving you.
Right now, begin to confess your freedom -
I am restored. I am reinstated.
Confess you freedom.
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
TT: Juliet Bwalya 16/06/18